Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 31, Folder: 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employer-Employee Relations Activities of Trade Associations, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Trade Association Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report on Industrial Training Developments, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By The Department of Manufacture. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Papers Prepared for The National Symposium on Guaranteed Income, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. December 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What the 1949 Wage-Hour Act Means: Information about the Newly-Amended Law and a Summary of its Provisions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. November 1, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Explaining Your Buisness, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Buisness Relations Department. v.11:no.3 (1960:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Buisness Relations Department. v.11:no.2 (1960:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Business Relations Department. v.11:no.1 (1960:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.4 (1960:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.5 (1960:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.6 (1960:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.7 (1960:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.8 (1960:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.9 (1960:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.10 (1960:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.11 (1960:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.11:no.12 (1960:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.1 (1961:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.2 (1961:Ferb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.3 (1961:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.4 (1961:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.5 (1961:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.6 (1961:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.7 (1961:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.8 (1961:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.9 (1961:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.10 (1961:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.11 (1961:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.12:no.12 (1961:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Explaining Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. v.13:no.1 (1962:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Box: 31, Folder: 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Infaltion's Helpmate: The Davis-Bacon and Walsh-Healey Acts, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Looking Forward in Labor Relations; a talk before the Rochester Chamber of Commerce, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    By C.E. Wilson. Wednesday, June 2, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Profits; what are they who gets them why, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Delivered Pricing and the Law, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Case for Voluntary Unionism; a discussion of the merits of "right-towork" lows and the dangers of complusory unionism, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Forward America; A Process for Mobilizing Total Community Resources, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Policy Declarations on Economic Security; Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Investment for Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Investment for Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Economics of Minimum Wage Legislation; Report on the Committee on Economic Policy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Labor-Management Relations Today; an Adress by Herman W. Steinkraus, President, Chamber of Commerce of the United States Before the Annual Meeting of the American Mining Congress, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    By Herman W. Steinkraus. Spokane, September 29, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Financial Survey of the Major National and International Unions of the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: The Labor Crisis, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: The Drive for a Controlled Economy via Pale Pink Pills, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Buisness Management Action Against Depression; Danger Signs, Some Do's and Don'ts; a guide Prepared by The Committee on Economic Policy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Economics of Minimum Wage Legislation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: How to Stop Strikes; A broadcast over the red netwrok of the National Broadcasting Company, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    By Albert W. Hawkes; John Q. Carey; Edmund Ruffin. Friday evening, July 18, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Guide to Equal Pay Act, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Inflation's Helpmate; the Davis-Bacon and Walsh-Healy Acts, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: The Personnel Practices Guide; Industrial Relations in America, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Buisness Management and Economic Analysis; Report of Committee on Economic Policy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: The Point Four Program; A Business Viewpoint on the President's Plan for Economic Advancement of Underdeveloped Areas, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Federal Wage-Hour Law; Report of Department of Manufacture Committee, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. January 26, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Leadership and Service; Progress Report of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Box: 31, Folder: 6 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How to Strengthen Employee Loyalty With Letters, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: A Checklist on Employee Pension Plans for Use by Employers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Ratification of I.L.O. Conventions by the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Distribution: A Key to High Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Employment of Physically Handicapped And Older Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Another Round of Wage Increases and the Employment Outlook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Box: 31, Folder: 7 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 34th Annual Meeting: Address, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Selected Reference, Pro and Con: The "Right-To-Work", Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Books and Pamphlets. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Let's Discuss Employee Rights Under the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Labor Relations and Legal Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Equal Protection of Right-To-Work Laws, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Legal Relations and Legal Department. Extracts showing the protection afforded union membership as well as non-membership under right-to-work laws. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: State Laws on Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Labor Relations and Legal Department. A brief summary of the status and extent of laws banning compulsory union membership. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: State Right-To-Work Laws, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. A text of state laws phohibiting discrimination in employment because of membership or non-membership in a labor organization. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Right to Work vs. the Union Shop, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Information Bulletin, no.50 (1957). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Right to Work (Compulsory Unionism - Union Shop - Closed Shop), Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Information Bulletin, no.2 (1953). Revised 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Summary of Resolutions and Recommendations Adopted by the AFL and CIO Conventions in 1949, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: A New Need for Effective Citizenship, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Philip M. Talbott. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: A Challenge to Leadership in Business, Labor and Government, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: The Job of Selling America to the Americans, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: A Program for Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Herman W. Steinkraus, President and General Manager of the Bridgeport Brass Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations in America, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Employer-Employee Relations Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations in America: Policy Declarations, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Department of Manufacture. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Industrial Relations in America: Policy Declarations, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Statement of William B. Barton for the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By William B. Barton. Remarks before the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare with respect to S. 2650. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: A Realistic Appraisal of Distribution Problems, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chas. M. Isaac. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Government Employee Negotiations and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Secondary Boycotts, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Infromation Bulletin, no.15 (1954). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Testimony on unemployment and automation presented to a subcommittee on unemployment and automation of the Committee on Education and Labor, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Emerson P. Schmidt. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Testimony on Amendment to the Davis-Bacon Act and the Eight Hour Laws Presented to a House Labor Subcommittee, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Lee E. Knack. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: A Shorter Workweek? An Information Manual on Key Questions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Fiftieth Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: The Hidden Payroll: Non-Wage Labor Costs of Doing Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: 39th Annual Meeting: Address, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By L. W. Horning. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Policy Declarations: Industrial Relations in America, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Analysis of Workmen's Compensation Laws, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: How to Organize a Public Affairs Program in Your Business, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Advertisement. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, Folder: 8 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Program for Sustaining Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Second edition. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Program for Sustaining Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Second edition. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The American Competitive Enterprise System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The Economics of the Money Supply, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Toward Worker Security: The Role of Management, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Sopy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Model Arbitration Clauses to Protect Management Rights., Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: A Program For Sustraining Employment: Report of Committee on Economic Policy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The Economics of the Guaranteed Wage: report of Committee on Economic Policy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Federal Grants-in-Aid: The Anatomy of The Problem, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Economic Policies for National Defense, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Labor Organizations in great Britian: Legislative Restrictions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: How Much Can Our Economy Stand?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Policy Declarations of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: The American Competitive Enterprise System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Steadier Jobs: An Action Program for Management, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Business Management and Economic Analysis, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Toward Worker Security: The Role of management, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Unemployment: the nature of the challenge, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: The Economics of The Guaranteed Wage, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Communism: Where do we stand today?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: Group Action and its Impact on the Nation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: The American Competitive Enterprise System, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Spending and Taxing: A study in Economic principles and Human Well-Being, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: Adventures in Thinking: One Jump Ahead: A story of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Better Business Relations Through Employee Meetings, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box: 31, Folder: 9 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations Letter, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. no.115 (1954:Jan.)-v.3:no.13 (1960:Dec.). Includes Secondary Boycott Series Bulletin, no.1-9 (1954). Item is in English.
- Box: 31, Folder: 10 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Urban Action Exchange, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. A voluntary effort by National organizations to share action programs that can help meet the urban crisis. Item is in English.
- Box: 31, Folder: 11 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: County-Wide Plan Controls Dayton Area Pollution Problem, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.11. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Indianapolis Chamber Leads in Upgrading Policy Quality, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.12. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Winston-Salem Park Plan Serves Recreation Needs For All, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.10. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Detroit Industries Become Partners of Core City High School, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.9. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Boston Firm Marking Ten Years of Success in Hiring Hard Core, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.8. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Philadelphia Utility Offers Jobs And Advancement to Minorities, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.7. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Rochester Business Opportunities Corporation Helps Ghetto Dwellers Own Businesses, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Rochester, Minnesota Mobilizes To Meet Total Area Needs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Jacksonville, Florida, Merges City and Country Governments, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Hartford Fund Guides and Finances Low-Cost Housing, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Buffalo Employs the Hard Core with Opportunities Developnment Corporation, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Omaha Puts Youth to Work in Project Y.E.S., Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Case Study no.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Case Studies Show How Local leaders Attack urban Ills, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    By Urban Action Clearinghouse. Item is in English.
- Box: 32, Folder: 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Publications of the Economic Research Department, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. July, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Publications of the Economic Research Department, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. February, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Publications of the Economic Research Department, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. April, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Publications of the Economic Research Department, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. November, 1953. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Spending and Taxing, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: You Showed Your Interest, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By William J. Malatesta. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Church Looks at Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Labor and the American Economy: A Study in Economic Principles and Human Well-Being, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Law in the Public Interest: A Statement of National Chamber policy on revisions in the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Adjustment of Labor Disputes in Defense Industries: Committee Report, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Can Government Guarantee Full Employment?: Post War Readjustments, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Bulletin No. 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Investment for Jobs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Why Discuss? The American Competitive Enterprise Economy-a new economics primer designed for adult discussion, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The Davis-Bacon Act: Questions and Answers on this Shotgun Law, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: The Facts About Common Situs Secondary Boycotts, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: The Walsh-Healey Act: Questions and Answers on this Horse and Buggy Law, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Guide to Civil Rights Act: An Analysis of titles II,VI, and XI, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Building A Retirenment Plan, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Joshua B. Glasser. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Wanted: Men. Development Business leadership through Economics Discussion Groups, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: How Competitive is the American Economy, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Progress and Prosperity, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The National Income and its distribution, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 4. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Money, Income and Jobs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Wage Drives and the Outlook for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Individual and Group Security, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Social Security Medicare, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Guide to Equal Pay Act, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: A Charter for Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Eric A. Johnston. Reprinted from The New York Times Magazine. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Officers Directors Committeemen of the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. 1956-1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: For the Long-Range Good of America, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Free Markets and Free Men, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: The Economies of The Guaranteed Wage, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Labor's Impact on Transportation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Should Labor be Drafted?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: The National Income and its Distribution, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Number 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Publications of the Economic Research Department, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. November, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: A Multi-Billion Dollar Opportunity, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)